RG 041:002, Public Utilities Commission
Connecticut State Library
Public Utilities Commission records
1911-1988, bulk 1911-1976
Connecticut State Library
Connecticut. Public Utilities Commission
178.25 cubic feet
The Public Utilities Commission began on September 9, 1911. In 1975 it became the Public Utilities Control Authority.
RG041_002
Multiple
Historical Note
In 1911, the General Assembly established the Public Utilities Commission by consolidating the duties of the railroad commissioners and the inspector general of gas meters and illuminating gas. Its responsibilities included nearly all public power, transportation and communication facilities. In 1975, the General Assembly created the Public Utilities Control Authority from the former Public Utilities Commission. In 1979 this became the Division of Public Utility Control in the Dept. of Business Regulation and in 1980 was made an independent department called the Dept. of Public Utility Control.
See also the.
See also the.
Scope and Content
Series 1. Record Books, 1911-1946, include Commission decisions, findings, and orders issued in response to petitions, applications, and appeals made by corporations, municipalities, and individuals. The record books for steam railroads and street railways also include permissions to run special trains and statements of inspection.
Series 2. Annual Reports from Companies, 1911-1949, contain information on but not limited to the following: the organization, directors and officers, stockholding, areas of operation, finances, freight moved, equipment owned.
Series 3. Docket Maps, 1869-1949, bulk 1911-1941, are of projected rights of way and changes to established lines, grade-crossing elimination plans, blueprints for stations and bridges, both for railroads and street railways.
Series 4. Special Commission for the Investigation of Problems Relating to the Street Railways, 1918-1919, include two volumes of hearing transcripts and exhibits.
Series 5. Dockets, 1911-1988, has three subseries: rail, bus and taxicab livery, and index cards. Rail dockets include applications and petitions along with findings and orders, as well as accident investigation reports. Bus and taxicab livery dockets contain primarily applications and decisions concerning routes and fares. Some of the bus and livery dockets date to the time of the Public Utilities Commission's successor agency, the Public Utilities Control Authority. The index cards provide an access point to both the rail and the bus and taxicab livery dockets.
Series 6. Daily Log Books, 1948-1976, is comprised of 35 volumes that record hearings held and documents issued.
Series 7. Miscellaneous records, 1911-1924, is comprised primarily of correspondence, petitions, and receipts.
Arrangement
Arranged into seven series as follows:
Series 1. Record books, 1911-1946, is arranged by type of company and then chronologically. Companies include: steam railroads and street railways; electric, gas, telephone, telegraph, water and exp.; jitneys or motor vehicles; taxicabs; trucking.
Series 2. Annual reports from companies, 1911-1949, is arranged by type of company and then chronologically. Companies include: jitneys; motor bus operators; motor truck operators; railroad and express companies; street railways; taxicab operators. Not all years are present for each type of company.
Series 3. Maps, 1869-1949, bulk 1911-1941, are arranged numerically.
Series 4. Special Commission for an Investigation of Problems Relating to the Street Railways, 1918-1919.
Series 5. Dockets, 1911-1988, is arranged in three subseries: rail regulatory dockets, bus and taxi livery dockets, and docket index cards. Rail regulatory dockets are arrranged by docket number. The bus and taxi livery dockets are also by docket number beginning with box 7 except for the last box. The docket index cards are arranged by town and then by docket number.
Series 6. Daily log books, 1948-1976, are arranged chronologically.
Series 7. Miscellaneous records, 1911-1924.
Related Material
RG 041:001, Board of Railroad Commissioners, circa 1848-1912, bulk 1854-1911
RG 041:003, Connecticut Siting Council, 1975-1992
RG 041:004, Public Utilities Control Authority, 1975-1976
Index Terms
Organizations:
Connecticut. Public Utilities Commission; Connecticut. Special Commission for an Investigation of Problems Relating to the Street Railways; Connecticut. Public Utilities Control Authority
Subjects:
Public utilities -- Law and legislation -- Connecticut; Railroads -- Connecticut -- Maps; Railroads -- Law and legislation -- Connecticut; Street-railroads -- Connecticut -- Maps; Street-railroads -- Law and legislation -- Connecticut; Buses -- Fares -- Connecticut; Taxicabs -- Fares -- Connecticut; Taxicabs -- Law and legislation -- Connecticut; Trucking -- Law and legislation -- Connecticut
Document Types:
Correspondence; Dockets;; Reports; Logbooks
Restrictions on Access
These records are stored at an off-site facility and therefore may not be available on a same-day basis.
See the policy.
Container List
- Series 1. Record books, 1911-1946; 6 cubic feet (31 volumes); 1972-004
  - Organizational matters
    - 1911 September 9 - 1942 February 20 (Volume Volume 1)
      Includes approvals of forms for annual reports; correspondence; resolution honoring Goeorge M, Woodruff, May 5, 1930; list of Public Utitilities Commission employees since 1911 with titles, dates of employment and remarks (deceased or resigned), July 1, 1933; minutes; and appointments.
  - Steam railroads and street railways
    - 1911 September 9 - 1912 September 24 (Volume Volume 1)
    - 1912 September 24 - 1913 May 10 (Volume Volume 2)
    - 1913 May 10 - 1914 January 19 (Volume Volume 3)
    - 1914 January 19 - 1914 November 6 (Volume Volume 4)
    - 1914 November 24 - 1916 January 3 (Volume Volume 5)
    - 1916 January 3 - 1916 September 7 (Volume Volume 6)
    - 1916 September 8 - 1917 July 3 (Volume Volume 7)
    - 1917 July 10 - 1919 January 24 (Volume Volume 8)
    - 1919 January 31 - 1920 December 20 (Volume Volume 9)
    - 1920 December 20 - 1923 April 3 (Volume Volume 10)
    - 1923 April 11 - 1925 January 12 (Volume Volume 11)
    - 1925 January 17 - 1926 October 28 (Volume Volume 12)
    - 1926 November 17 - 1928 July 18 (Volume Volume 13)
    - 1928 July 2 - 1930 January 31 (Volume Volume 14)
    - 1929 December 26 - 1932 April 27 (Volume Volume 15)
    - 1932 April 18 - 1936 July 31 (Volume Volume 16)
    - 1936 August 7 - 1940 April 12 (Volume Volume 17)
    - 1940 May 21 - 1946 October 14 (Volume Volume 18)
      Spine is blank.
  - Electric, gas, telephone, telegraph, water and exp.
    - 1911 September 9 - 1919 March 20 (Volume Volume 1)
    - 1919 April 29 - 1923 October 24 (Volume Volume 2)
    - 1923 November 1 - 1928 May 17 (Volume Volume 3)
    - 1928 June 5 - 1933 January 27 (Volume Volume 4)
    - 1933 February 3 - 1936 December 11 (Volume Volume 5)
    - 1936 November 25 - 1942 March 17 (Volume Volume 6)
    - 1941 July 31 - 1945 July 27 (Volume Volume 7)
  - Jitneys or motor vehicles
    - 1921 June 17 - 1931 January 27 (Volume Volume 1)
    - 1931 April 2 - 1938 August 26 (Volume Volume 2)
    - 1938 August 29 - 1945 November 21 (Volume Volume 3)
  - Taxicabs
    - 1929 November 4 - 1945 October 24 (Volume Volume 1)
  - Trucking
    - 1935 September 23 - 1946 May 15 (Volume Volume 1)
- Series 2. Annual Reports from Companies, 1911-1949; 9 cubic feet; 2003-034
  - Jitneys (Box 1)
    - Volume 1, Arganse to Kelly, 1929 (Box 1)
    - Volume 2, Leclair - White Line Bus Corporation, 1929 (Box 1)
    - Volume 1, Arganse - Kolesnik, 1930 (Box 1)
  - Motor bus operators (Box 1)
    - 1931, 1 volume (Box 1)
    - 1932, 1 volume (Box 1)
    - 1937, 1 volume (Box 1)
    - 1938, 1 volume (Box 1)
    - 1941, 1 volume (Box 2)
    - Small, 1941; 1 volume (Box 2)
    - Small, 1942; 1 volume (Box 2)
  - Motor truck operators (Box 2)
    - Volume 1, 1941; 1 volume (Box 2)
    - Volume 2, 1944; 1 volume (Box 3)
    - Volume 3, 1944; 1 volume (Box 3)
  - Railroad companies (Box 3)
    - 1911, 1 volume (Box 3)
    - 1919, 1 volume (Box 3)
  - Railroads and express companies (Box 4)
    - 1915, 1 volume (Box 4)
    - 1918, 1 volume (Box 4)
    - 1924, 1 volume (Box 4)
    - 1925, 1 volume (Box 5)
    - 1933, 1 volume (Box 5)
    - 1937, 1 volume (Box 5)
    - 1940, 1 volume (Box 5)
    - 1941, 1 volume (Box 5)
  - Railroads, street railways and express companies (Box 6)
    - 1949, 1 volume (Box 6)
  - Street railway companies (Box 6)
    - 1911, 1 volume (Box 6)
    - 1912, 1 volume (Box 6)
    - 1914, 1 volume (Box 6)
    - 1915, 1 volume (Box 6)
    - 1918, 1 volume (Box 7)
    - 1919, 1 volume (Box 7)
    - 1925, 1 volume (Box 7)
    - 1936, 1 volume (Box 8)
    - 1938, 1 volume (Box 8)
    - 1939, 1 volume (Box 8)
  - Taxicab operators (Box 8)
    - Small, 1936; 1 volume (Box 8)
    - Large, 1936; 1 volume (Box 8)
    - Small, 1937; 1 volume (Box 8)
    - Large, 1937; 1 volume (Box 8)
    - Small, 1938; 1 volume (Box 8)
    - Large, 1938; 1 volume (Box 8)
    - Small, 1941; 1 volume (Box 8)
    - Large, 1942; 1 volume (Box 8)
    - 1949, 1 volume (Box 8)
- Series 3. Docket Maps, 1869-1949, bulk 1911-1941; 16 cubic feet; 1986-068
  Numbered 1-1164
  Listing available at History & Genealogy Reference desk. These items are identified on the listing with the code "PUC". The listing also include maps, charts, and blueprints submitted pre-1911 to the Board of Railroad Commissioners as well as those removed from RG 041:001, Board of Railroad Commissioners, Series 3 and 5 during processing.
- Series 4. Special Commission for an Investigation of Problems Relating to the Street Railways, 1918-1919; .5 cubic feet (2 volumes); 1921-041
  - Records, 1918-1919 (Box Vol. 1-2)
    Hearing transcripts and exhibits.
- Series 5. Dockets, 1911-1988; 135.75 cubic feet
  - Accession: 1985-008, 1911-1974
    Rail regulatory dockets.
    Arranged by docket number.
    The index cards in Accession 1885-009 Boxes 19 and 20 provide an access point to the dockets.
    - 1-122, 1911-1912 (Box 1)
    - 125-231, 1912 (Box 2)
    - 234-342, 1912 (Box 3)
    - 344-446, 1912 (Box 4)
    - 453-571, 1912 (Box 5)
    - 574-660, 1912 (Box 6)
    - 661-737, 1913 (Box 7)
    - 743-819, 1913 (Box 8)
    - 823-921, 1913 (Box 9)
    - 922-1003, 1913 (Box 10)
    - 1004-1080, 1913 (Box 11)
    - 1084-1172, 1913-1916 (Box 12)
    - 1178-1327, 1914 (Box 13)
    - 1334-1427, 1914 (Box 14)
    - 1429-1535, 1914-1916 (Box 15)
    - 1536-1660, 1914-1915 (Box 16)
    - 1662-1750, 1915 (Box 17)
    - 1752-1833, 1915-1916 (Box 18)
    - 1835-1907, 1916 (Box 19)
    - 1912-2053, 1916 (Box 20)
    - 2058-2190, 1916 (Box 21)
    - 2191-2264, 1917 (Box 22)
    - 2266-2338, 1917 (Box 23)
    - 2343-2499, 1917 (Box 24)
    - 2500-2611, 1917 (Box 25)
    - 2612-2823, 1917 (Box 26)
    - 2766-2816, 1965-1969 (Box 26A)
    - 2828-2965, 1931 (Box 27)
    - 2967-3148, 1918 (Box 28)
    - 31349-3287, 1919 (Box 29)
    - 3293-3408, 1920 (Box 30)
    - 3412-3569, 1920 (Box 31)
    - 3573-3717, 1921 (Box 32)
    - 3718-3909, 1921 (Box 33)
    - 3910-4066, 1922 (Box 34)
    - 4067-4169, 1921 (Box 35)
    - 4170-4235, 1923-1924 (Box 36)
    - 4236-4321, 1923-1924 (Box 37)
    - 4323-4388, 1924 (Box 38)
    - 4389-4512, 1924 (Box 39)
    - 4513-4580, 1925 (Box 40)
    - 4582-4684, 1925 (Box 41)
    - 4685-4818, 1926 (Box 42)
    - 4819-4920, 1929 (Box 43)
    - 4921-5061, 1927 (Box 44)
    - 5064-5165, 1927 (Box 45)
    - 5168-5249, 1928 (Box 46)
    - 5251-5321, 1929 (Box 47)
    - 5322-5422, 1929 (Box 48)
    - 5247-5530, 1930 (Box 49)
    - 5587-5873, 1931 (Box 50)
    - 5874-6054, 1933 (Box 51)
    - 6059-6219, 1934 (Box 52)
    - 6222-6421, 1935 (Box 53)
    - 6426-6563, 1936-1937 (Box 54)
    - 6564-6763, 1937-1939 (Box 55)
    - 6764-6939, 1939-1940 (Box 56)
    - 6944-7117, 1940-1941 (Box 57)
    - 7119-7280, 1941-1942 (Box 58)
    - 7283-7485, 1942-1944 (Box 59)
    - 7486-7690, 1944-1945 (Box 60)
    - 7292-7850, 1942-1946 (Box 61)
    - 7852-7995, 1946-1947 (Box 62)
    - 7996-8137, 1948 (Box 63)
    - 8140-8266, 1948-1950 (Box 64)
    - 8271-8416, 1949-1951 (Box 65)
    - 8421-8578, 1950-1951 (Box 66)
    - 8585-8787, 1951-1953 (Box 67)
    - 8793-9003, 1953-1954 (Box 68)
    - 9004-9304, 1954-1955 (Box 69)
    - 9305-9371, 1955-1958 (Box 70)
    - 9371-9562, 1958-1957 (Box 71)
    - 9564-9744, 1957-1959 (Box 72)
    - 9745-9884, 1959-1960 (Box 73)
    - 9910-10117, 1960-1963 (Box 74)
    - 10123-10218, 1963 (Box 75)
    - 10218-10269, 1963-1964 (Box 76)
    - 10276-10380, 1964-1965 (Box 77)
    - 10382-10498, 1965-1966 (Box 78)
    - 10505-10593, 1966-1967 (Box 79)
    - 10602-10688, 1967 (Box 80)
    - 10711-10834, 1968-1969 (Box 81)
    - 10835-10972, 1969-1970 (Box 82)
    - 10982-11249, 1970-1972 (Box 83)
    - 11261-11514, 1972-1974 (Box 84)
  - Accession: 1985-009, 1939-1980
    Bus and taxi livery dockets.
    - Bus & Taxi Livery - Complaints, 1977-1979 (Box 1)
    - Bus & Taxi Livery - Hearings of Arrow Line Bus, 1978-1980 (Box 2)
    - Bus & Taxi Livery - The Connecticut Co. (Box 3)
      - Hartford Local - Charter Oak Ave., undated (Box 3, Folder R140)
      - Hartford - East Hartford - Glastonbury (Brewer Street), 1963, 1971, 1972 (Box 3, Folder R141)
      - New Haven Local (Appl. 2358), 1955, 1956, 1957, 1962 (Box 3, Folder R143)
      - West Haven Local (Jones Hill Rd), 1939, 1940, 1948, 1952, 1967 (Box 3, Folder R144)
      - Hartford - Wethersfield (C-200)- Franklin Avenue, 1950, 1952, 1953, 1963, 1964 (Box 3, Folder R145)
      - Hartford - Bloomfield (C-200) - Blue Hills Avenue, 1961, 197 (Box 3, Folder R146)
      - East Hartford Local - Tolland Street (Appl. 2350), 1960, 1962 (Box 3, Folder R147)
      - New Haven - Branford (C-200) (Appl. 2474 - Amendment 313), 1964, 1971 (Box 3, Folder R149)
      - New Haven - Middletown - Meriden - Hartford - Lake Compound (Appl. 3037), 1946 (Box 3, Folder R155)
      - Rocky Hill (Ct. Foundery), 1947 (Box 3, Folder R159)
      - Extension of School Routes in Hartford & Glastonbury, 1963, 1966 (Box 3, Folder R208)
      - New Haven Locals - Abandoned Street Railway Service (C-200), 1970, 1961, 1962, 1964 (Box 3, Folder R167, R 172)
      - East Hartford Local (Sunset Ridge School) (C-200), 1964 (Box 3, Folder R173)
      - Hartford Local (Hartford Hospital) (C-200) (Appl. 3337 temporary Amendment 6/13/49 made permanent 3/22/51, 1950, 1951 (Box 3, Folder R179)
      - Darien Local (Appl 3561) TFR of (C-200)- CT. Co. (R43 from C.R. and L), 1953 (Box 3, Folder R183)
      - Hartford Local - Cross Town (C-200), 1963 (Box 3, Folder R185)
      - Stamford Local (High Ridge C-200) Appl. 4341, 1963 (Box 3, Folder R187)
      - New Haven Mount Carmel - Waterbury (C-200) Appl. 4561, 1970 (Box 3, Folder R188)
      - New Haven - Hammonasset Beach - Madison (C-200) Appl. 4618, 1968 (Box 3, Folder R205)
      - Cancelled Amendment 668, 1970 (Box 3, Folder R 191-195, 198 Docket 10718)
      - Manchester - Hartford (C-200) Appl. (Box 3, Folder R206 MISC)
    - Bus 8 Trailways 4853 - Greyhound 4856 (Box 4)
    - Bus and Taxi Livery/Truck Notes, 1963, 1974, 1976 (Box 5)
    - Bus & Taxi Livery, 1975,1978, 1979 (Box 6)
    - The Short Line of CT., Inc. of Rocky Hill - To increase fares, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 10572)
    - Charles R. Bell, Branford Cab - To increase fares, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 10669)
    - Southington Taxi Service, Inc. - increase school childrens fares, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 10672)
    - Thames Valley Transit, Inc. - Commutation fares, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 10673)
    - Thames Valley Transportation, Inc. of Norwich commutation fares, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 10674)
    - The Bridgeport Auto Transit Co. - increase bus fares, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 10678)
    - Harvey R. Galaise of Winsted - increase cab fare, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 10682)
    - Arrow Line, Inc. of East Hartford - increase bus fares, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 10694)
    - Town & Country Yellow Cab Co. of New Britain - increase taxicab fares, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 10695)
    - The Chestnut Hill Bus Corp. of Bridgeport - increase bus fares, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 10702)
    - Silver Lane Bus Line - Transfer stock from Edward M. Royce to George A. Negro of Bolton, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 10704)
    - Cooke St. Line, Inc. of Waterbury - increase in bus fares, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 10708)
    - The Town Taxi Co. of Stratford - increase cab fares, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 10714)
    - The Conn. Co - to discontinue bus service in the Meriden - Middletown Division, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 10718)
    - The Norwich City Cab Co. - to increase fares, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 10716)
    - Gray Line Bus Co. of Bridgeport - to increase fare on Bridgeport - Trumbull route, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 10719)
    - The Terminal Taxi Co. of New Haven - increase cab fares, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 10720)
    - The Bridgeport Auto Transit Co. - to change token rates of fare, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 10724)
    - Santiago Saitta Taxi of Colchester - to increase taxi and livery fares, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 10730)
    - Edward Stankoski, DBA Newington Taxi Service - to increase fares, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 10732)
    - The Hickey Cab Co. of Bridgeport - Transfer of Stock, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 10741)
    - The East Hartford Cab Co. - to increase cab fares, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 10743)
    - The Waterbury Yellow Cab and Service Co. - increase fares, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 10744)
    - New London Taxi cab Operators - increase fares, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 10745)
    - City Bus Line Inc. of Torrington - increase motor bus fares, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 10747)
    - The Yellow Cab Co., of Torrington, Inc. - increase fares, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 10748)
    - Davenport Taxi of Stratford - increase fares, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 10749)
    - Yellow Cab of Bristol - to increase fares, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 10756)
    - The Conn. Co. - curtail service and increase fares on the Hartford - Silver Lane - Manchester route, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 10767)
    - The Winsted Yellow Cab Co. - to increase fares, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 10770)
    - New Britain Transportation Co. - increase bus fares, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 10775)
    - The Conn. Railways & Lighting Co. of Bridgeport - to abandon Norwalk Division Routes, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 10781)
    - Stanley S. Barstow, DBA Barstow Transportation of Dayville - increase bus fares, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 10785)
    - James W. Munsie, DBA Nutmeg Bus Lines of Thompsonville - of Thompsonville - for increase in commutation bus fares between Enfield and East Hartford Enfield and East Hartford, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 10788)
    - The Meriden Yellow Cab Co., Inc. - increase fares, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 10809)
    - The Keating Taxi Co. of Danbury - to increase fares, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 10818)
    - Walter S. Dean of Old Lyme - increase taxi cab rates of fares, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 10820)
    - Maurice H. Clark of Essex - to increase taxi cab rates of fares, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 10821)
    - The Conn. Co. - to incur debt of $165,000, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 10823)
    - Yellow Cab of Middletown, Inc. - to increase taxi cab rates of fares, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 10825)
    - McCann Associates, Inc. DBA City Cab of Milford - to increase taxi cab fares, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 10826)
    - Corbin Ave. Bus Service of Bridgeport - to increase fares, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 10843)
    - Gray Line Bus Co., Inc. of Bridgeport - to increase fares, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 10845)
    - The Conn. Co. - to establish exact fare system in Hartford, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 10847)
    - Greenwich Taxi, Inc. - to increase taxi cab rates of fares, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 10853)
    - New London Taxi cab Operators - to increase fares, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 10854)
    - National Bus Traffic Association, Inc., Agent for Arrow Lines, Inc. of East Hartford - to increase motor bus fares, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 10856)
    - National Bus Traffic Association, Inc., Agent for Greyhound Lines, Inc. of Cleveland, Ohio - increase motor bus fares, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 10857)
    - National Bus Traffic Association, Inc., Agent for Super Service Coach Corp. of New York, N.Y. - increase motor bus fares, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 10858)
    - City Cab Service, Inc. of Hartford - to increase taxi cab fares for all Hartford Operators, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 10866)
    - Transfer of the Keating Taxi Co. of Danbury to Howard Morris and Geral Crocco, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 10873)
    - Town and Country Yellow Cab Co., Inc. of New Britian - to increase taxi cab fares, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 10874)
    - Northeast Transportation Co. of Waterbury - to increase bus fares, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 10880)
    - Independent Cab Co. of Naugatuck - to increase taxi cab fares, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 10886)
    - The Blue Line, Inc. of Windham - increase bus fares, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 10924)
    - The Conn. Co. - schedule changes in the Hartford division, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 10927)
    - The Orange St. Bus Line Co., Inc. of New Haven - to increase fares, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 10933)
    - The East Hartford Cab Co. - to increase cab fares, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 10936)
    - The Conn. Railway and Lighting Co. - schedule changes in Bridgeport and New Britain, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 10936)
    - The Hickey Cab Co., of Bridgeport - to increase taxi cab fares for Bridgeport Operators, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 10939)
    - The Conn. Railway Lighting Co. - to charge for transfers, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 10964)
    - Conn. - New York Airport Bus Co., Inc. of Milford - to abandon service between New Haven and Hartford, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 10976)
    - Overland Corp. of North America, Inc. of West Haven - abandonment of all limousine bus service from authorized points in Conn. to Bradley Field, Windsor Locks Field, Windsor Locks, 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 10978)
    - Westport Taxi Service, Inc. and Teddy's Westport Taxi, Inc. - to increase taxi cab fares, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 10983)
    - New Haven and Shoreline Railway Co., Inc., DBA Savin Bus Lines of New London - to abandon motor bus service between New London and Niantic - Crescent Beach (East Lyme) Niantic - Crescent Beach (East Lyme), 1970 (Box 9, Folder 10986)
    - The Airfield Service Co. of Windsor Locks - to increase taxi and livery fares, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 10995)
    - A.B.C. Transportation, Inc. of West Redding - to discontinue bus operations (Danbury - Bethel - Ridgefield), 1970 (Box 9, Folder 11002)
    - Davenport Taxi, Inc. DBA Davenpark Taxi of Stamford - to increase fares, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 11012)
    - Southington Taxi Service, Inc. - to increase fares, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 11013)
    - Connecticut Railway and Lighting Co. - to increase fares, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 11028)
    - The Hickey Cab Company of Bridgeport - to prescribe increase taxi cab fares for all Bridgeport Operators cab fares for all Bridgeport Operators, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 11072)
    - New Haven and Shore Line Railway Co., Inc., DBA Savin Bus Lines - to discontinue service in Norwich to discontinue service in Norwich, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 11079)
    - Dattco, Inc. of New Britain - to increase bus fares, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 11083)
    - The East Hartford Cab Co. - to increase taxi cab fares, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 11086)
    - The Bridgeport Auto Transit Co. - to increase bus fares, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 11097)
    - Rockville Cab Co. - to increase cab fares, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 11098)
    - Conn. Railway and Lighting Co. - to curtail service, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 11103)
    - The National Bus Traffic Association, Inc., Agent for the Arrow Line, Inc. of East Hartford - to increase fares Line, Inc. of East Hartford - to increase fares, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 11108)
    - Super Service Coach Corp., New York, N.Y. - to increase bus fares, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 11109)
    - The Trumbull Cab Co. - to increase fares, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 11118)
    - The Conn. Co. - to curtail service in Hartford and New Haven, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 11119)
    - Fairfield Taxi Service, Inc. - increase taxi and livery fares, 1911-1972 (Box 9, Folder 11216)